Guide to the Wunderman Archives, 1946-2010 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Wunderman Archives 1946-2010 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Wunderman.
520 linear feet Extent: 354,000 Items
Wunderman is a direct marketing and behavior-oriented marketing communications firm founded in 1958 as Wunderman Ricotta & Kline. It is currently a subsidiary of the Young & Rubicam agency. The Wunderman Archives span the years 1946-2010 and comprise the administrative records of direct-mail and direct marketing agency Wunderman and its predecessor entities Wunderman Ricotta & Kline, Wunderman Worldwide, Wunderman Cato Johnson, and Impiric, as well as its subsidiary offices in the U.S. and abroad, associated firms such as Stone & Adler and Chapman Direct, and its relations with parent company Young & Rubicam. It includes general office files, policy and procedure manuals, training materials, awards, account files, new business records, professional papers of founder Lester Wunderman and other key executives, samples of client campaigns, photographs, slides and audio cassettes and videocassettes. Clients include American Express, Apple, Army/ROTC, AT&T, Britannica Press, CBS, CIT Financial, Citibank, Columbia House, Ford, Gevalia Kaffe (Kraft), the Grolier Society, IBM, Jackson & Perkins, Johnson & Johnson, Lincoln-Mercury, Manufacturers Hanover Trust, Microsoft, Miller beer, National Rifle Association, New York Telephone/NYNEX, Time (Fortune, Money and Sports Illustrated magazines), Time-Life Books, United States Postal Service (USPS), and Xerox. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
RL.01416
Language: Material in English Arabic Catalan Chinese Czech Danish Dutch Finnish French German Greek Hungarian Italian Japanese Norwegian Portuguese Spanish Swedish Turkish
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is restricted.
Unpublished materials are closed to non-Wunderman researchers for 15 years from the date of creation.
Original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Research Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Wunderman Archives were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2010-2012.
Biographical Note
Chronology List
1958 Wunderman Ricotta & Kline (WRK) founded when Lester Wunderman, Irving Wunderman, Ed Ricotta and Harry Kline depart the Maxwell Sackheim & Co. advertising agency
1968 Open offices in Canada, London, Paris
1973 WRK merged with Young & Rubicam
1987 WRK name change to Wunderman Worldwide
1992 Wunderman Worldwide merger with Cato Johnson to form Wunderman Cato Johnson (WCJ)
1998 Lester Wunderman retired from WCJ
2000 WCJ name change to Impiric
2001 Impiric name change to Wunderman
2003 Acquisition of media planning agency Mediaedge:cia
2005 Acquisition of marketing analytics firm Fortelligent
2006 Acquisition of Seattle-based interactive services agency ZAAZ
2007 Acquisition of digital services agencies These Days (Belgium), Aqua Online (South Africa) and Blast Radius
2008 Acquisition of digital services agencies Actis Systems (Russia), Kassius (France) and DesignKitchen
Source: wunderman.com history timeline.
Collection Overview
The Wunderman Archives span the years 1946-2010 and comprise the administrative records of direct-mail and direct marketing agency Wunderman and its predecessor entities Wunderman Ricotta & Kline, Wunderman Worldwide, Wunderman Cato Johnson, and Impiric, as well as its subsidiary offices in the U.S. and abroad, associated firms such as Stone & Adler and Chapman Direct, and its relations with parent company Young & Rubicam. It includes general office files, policy and procedure manuals, training materials, awards, account files, new business records, professional papers of founder Lester Wunderman and other key executives, samples of client campaigns, photographs, slides and audio cassettes and videocassettes. Clients include American Express, Apple, Army/ROTC, AT&T, Britannica Press, CBS, CIT Financial, Citibank, Columbia House, Ford, Gevalia Kaffe (Kraft), the Grolier Society, IBM, Jackson & Perkins, Johnson & Johnson, Lincoln-Mercury, Manufacturers Hanover Trust, Microsoft, Miller beer, National Rifle Association, New York Telephone/NYNEX, Time (Fortune, Money and Sports Illustrated magazines), Time-Life Books, United States Postal Service (USPS), and Xerox.
Collection Arrangement
Collection is arranged into ten series: Administrative Files; Account Files; Awards; International Offices; New Business Files; Printed Materials; Print Advertising; Slides and Photographs; Training Materials and Presentations; and Audiovisual Materials. Original order was maintained and original folder titles were retained where practical. There is a degree of overlap of related material among some of the series, as between Account Files and International Offices, which reflects the historical record-keeping practices of the firm.
Subject Headings
Wunderman (Firm); Wunderman, Lester; American Express Company; American Telephone and Telegraph Company; Apple Computer, Inc.; Britannica Home Library Service; C.I.T. Financial Corporatin; Citibank (New York, N.Y.); Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc.; Columbia House (Firm); Ford Motor Company; Ford Motor Company. Lincoln-Mercury Division; International Business Machines Corporation; Jackson & Perkins Co; Johnson & Johnson; Kraft Foods Company; Manufacturers Hanover Trust Company; Microsoft Corporation; Miller Brewing Company; National Rifle Association of America; New York Telephone Company; Time, Inc.; Time-Life Books; United States. Army; United States. Army. Reserve Officers' Training Corps; United States Postal Service; Xerox Corporation; Young & Rubicam; Advertising; Advertising -- History; Advertising -- United States; Advertising, Direct-mail; Advertising, Direct-mail -- History; Advertising, Direct-mail -- United States; Advertising executives; Advertising executives -- United States; Direct marketing; Direct marketing -- History; Direct marketing -- United States; Audiocassettes; Negatives; Photographs; Slides; Videocassettes; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Separated Material
Enter Separated Material Note
The following digital items were removed from the collection:
1. Account Files. AT&T LEC and Asian GCN-OR-D02001. ZIP disc.
2. Account Files. AT&T World Traveler Summer Sweeps GCN-WT-098702. JAZ disc.
3. Account Files. Ford Merkur XR4TI Test Drive. 5.0 floppy disc.
4. International Offices--Argentina. SkyTel. 3.5 diskette.
5. International Offices--Canada. Xerox Digital Print Shop. 3.5 diskette.
6. International Offices--Italy. UNA Family. 3.5 diskette.
7. International Offices--Japan. IBM. 5.0 floppy disc.
8. International Offices--Japan. Dentsu WCJ internet advertisements. 1996. 3.5 diskette.
9. International Offices--Mexico. Ford Customer Communications disc 1. 1996. 3.5 diskette.
10. International Offices--Mexico. Ford Customer Communications disc 2. 1996. 3.5 diskette.
11. Account Files. Xerox Document Centre, presentation template and talk track. 3.5 diskette.
12. Account Files. Sony. ZIP disc.
13. Training Materials and Presentations. Phoenix Project. 3.5 diskette.
14. Training Materials and Presentations. Media Brands Case Study. 3.5 diskette.
15. Training Materials and Presentations. LATAM case studies. 3.5 diskette.
16. Training Materials and Presentations. Presentation Library 1-5. 3.5 diskette.
17. Training Materials and Presentations. Presentation Library 6-9. 3.5 diskette.
18. Training Materials and Presentations. Presentation Library 10-11. 3.5 diskette.
19. Training Materials and Presentations. Presentation templates. 3.5 diskette.
20. Training Materials and Presentations. O'Keefe Communications: Persuasion. Syquest cartridge.
21. Training Materials and Presentations. Lester Wunderman DMA speech backup. 3.5 diskette.
22. Training Materials and Presentations. Lester Wunderman short version of Toronto DMA speech. 3.5 diskette.
23. Awards. 1991 ECHO Awards. 3.5 diskette.
24. Awards. 1991 ECHO Awards. 3.5 diskette.
25. Awards. 1991 ECHO Awards. 3.5 diskette.
26. Awards. 1991 ECHO Awards. 3.5 diskette.
27. New Business. WCJ presentation templates, 1992. 3.5 diskette.
Related Material
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Abercrombie & Fitch Quarterly Catalog Collection
Arlie R. Slabaugh Collection of Direct Mail Literature
Charles McKinney Papers
Colored Mail Order Corporation of America records
J. Walter Thompson Company. Bertram Metter Papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Ronald B. Kaatz Papers
John Benjamin Harris Papers
Kensinger Jones Papers
Leo Bogart Papers
McGraw-Hill Marketing Information Center Vertical File
Sears, Roebuck and Company Catalog Collection.
Sheldon B. Sosna Papers
Superior Match Company matchbook advertising catalog and sales representative's forms
Detailed Description of Collection
- Administrative Files, 1955-2002 and undated, (18 boxes)
  Includes policy and procedure manuals, correspondence, vendor information and samples, article and clipping files, forms and stationery examples, corporate mission and strategy statements. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Archival storage records, 1981-1992, (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - General Files
    - Catalogs, 1984-1990 and undated, (5 folders) (Box 1)
    - Credit, articles, 1996-2000 (Box 1)
    - Publishing, 1988-1990 (Box 1)
    - Weight loss, articles, 1988-1990 (Box 1)
  - Arbeit and Company, profile, circa 1988 (Box 1)
  - Authenticum imaging, 1991 (Box 1)
  - AVI Visual Productions, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Bienfang, foamboard color samples, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Brilliant Image, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Cato Johnson Entertainment, circa 1990 (Box 2)
  - Envision slide imaging services, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Financial services, list of commercials and brochures, undated (Box 2)
  - MacForce (temp agency), 1991 (Box 2)
  - Perma Products storage files, undated (Box 2)
  - Princeton Creative Research, creativity testing, undated (Box 2)
  - Proofreader mark charts, undated (Box 2)
  - ProForma, cover binding samples, undated (Box 2)
  - Shana Corporation, Informed Manager, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Skillpath, Inc., 1992 (Box 2)
  - Slide Systems, Inc., imaging services, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Stone & Adler, 1981-1987 (Box 2)
  - Sudler & Hennessey backgrounder, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Visual Horizons buyer's guide, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Wunderman
    - Authority marketing, undated (Box 2)
    - Biographies of staff, undated (Box 2)
    - Consulting strategies, 1992 (Box 2)
    - Database marketing services, undated (Box 2)
    - File category listing, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Flow charts, undated (Box 3)
    - Forms, samples, 1978-1991 and undated (Box 3)
    - Fulfillment, undated (Box 3)
    - LAN/ReTix system, 1991 (Box 3)
    - LNA/Arbitron Multimedia Service, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous competitive, 1987-1989 and undated (Box 3)
    - Pet food case study, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Wunderman Cato Johnson (WCJ)
    - Case studies, circa 1997 (Box 3)
    - Corporate Identity Guidelines, undated (Box 3)
    - Creative Brief forms, undated (Box 3)
    - Credentials presentations, 1994-1995 and undated, (4 folders) (Box 3)
    - Direct Mail Production Manual, undated, (1 of 3 folders) (Box 3)
    - Direct Mail Production Manual, undated, (2-3 of 3 folders) (Box 4)
    - Information guide, undated (Box 4)
    - Merger/Vision statement, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 4)
    - Mike Becker Far East talk, credentials, undated (Box 4)
    - New and Emerging Laboratory, undated (Box 4)
    - Overview, 1995-1996 (Box 4)
    - Presentation library, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 4)
    - Resource Guide, undated (Box 5)
    - The Strategic Imperative to Merge Wunderman and Cato Johnson, 1992 (Box 5)
    - U.K. credentials, undated (Box 5)
    - WCJ Value Proposition, undated (Box 5)
    - Worldwide credentials and profiles, 1995-1997, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Worldwide Managers Meeting, Vol. II, 1995, (3 folders) (Box 5)
    - Worldwide Managers Meeting, Baden Baden, 1997, (1-7 of 10 folders) (Box 6)
    - Worldwide Managers Meeting, Baden Baden, 1997, (8-10 of 10 folders) (Box 7)
  - Wunderman International (Australia)
    - Profile, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Wunderman International Group (U.K.)
    - Credentials, undated (Box 7)
    - Directory of Direct Marketing, undated (Box 7)
    - Profile (Peter J. Rosenwald), 1978 (Box 7)
  - Wunderman, Ricotta & Kline
    - Credentials, 1986 (Box 7)
  - Wunderman Worldwide (WW)
    - Broadcast Traffic Procedures, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Credentials, 1990, (2 folders) (Box 7)
    - Forms, samples, 1989 and undated (Box 7)
    - Forms, samples, circa 1991, (3 folders) (Box 8)
    - Internship program, 1986-1990 (Box 8)
    - Kristen Butler chronological file, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
    - Managers Meeting, credentials, 1991, (4 folders) (Box 8)
    - Media miscellaneous, 1990 and undated (Box 9)
    - Media Research Alert, undated (Box 9)
    - Overview/Orientation, 1991 (Box 9)
    - Overview/Profile, 1990-1991 (Box 9)
    - Performance Appraisal, undated (Box 9)
    - Strategic Planning Model, undated (Box 9)
  - Young & Rubicam (Y&R)
    - Administrative Secretary guidelines, undated (Box 9)
    - AIM21 database service, 1994-1996 (Box 9)
    - Brand Asset Valuator, 1995 and undated (Box 9)
    - Database marketing, articles and case studies, 1984-1990 (Box 9)
    - Direct Marketing Group, credentials and overview, undated, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Forms, samples, undated (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-1992 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Whole Egg Concept, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Worldwide Brand Paradigms, 1994-1995 (Box 10)
    - Worldwide Product Committee VII, mini case histories, 1997 (Box 10)
    - Y&R Europe profile, undated (Box 10)
  - Y&R Article File
    - Action Marketing, undated (Box 10)
    - Action Marketing Basics (WCJ), undated (Box 10)
    - Action Marketing Principles, undated (Box 10)
    - Action Marketing Responding to Clients' Needs (WCJ), undated (Box 10)
    - Action Marketing Role (WCJ), undated (Box 10)
    - Action Marketing Worldwide Approach of WCJ, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Consumer Driven Direct Marketing, undated (Box 11)
    - Creative Process (WW), undated (Box 11)
    - Creativity, undated (Box 11)
    - Curriculum Marketing, undated (Box 11)
    - Curriculum Marketing--The Way of the Rat, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Database Core Practices, undated (Box 11)
    - Database marketing, articles and case studies, 1986-1992 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Demystifying Database and Curriculum Marketing, undated (Box 11)
    - Direct Marketing Chimera or Commitment (Edward Ney), 1981 (Box 11)
    - Direct Marketing miscellaneous, 1980s-1991, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - How to Recognize Great Advertising (Frazier Purdy), 1987, (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - Marketing development, undated (Box 12)
    - Newsletters, general information, 1980-1987 (Box 12)
    - Research--Application to Direct Marketing (Hugh Chambers), undated (Box 12)
    - Research--Cross Cultural Consumer Characterizations (4-C's), circa 1986 (Box 12)
    - Strategy--Consumer Perspective (Y&R), 1987 (Box 12)
    - Strategy--Demystfying the Strategic Planning Process (WW), undated (Box 12)
    - Strategy miscellaneous, undated (Box 12)
    - Strategy Selection, undated (Box 12)
    - Support Advertising, 1980s (Box 12)
    - Surveys, samples, 1990-1992 (Box 13)
    - Targeted Franchise Marketing, undated (Box 13)
    - Targeted Relationship Marketing (TRM), undated, (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - The Five Y&R Strategic Planning Tools, undated (Box 13)
    - Values and Lifestyle Segments (VALS), undated, (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Writing a Business Case (Harvard Business School), 1955 (Box 13)
    - Y&R Creative Work Plan, undated (Box 13)
  - Various Creative Samples
    - Booklets and brochures, undated (Box 14)
    - Flats, undated (Box 14)
    - Folders, undated (Box 14)
    - In-line formats and snap-packs, undated (Box 14)
    - Letter-sized packages, undated (Box 14)
    - Self-mailers and postcards, undated (Box 14)
    - Specialty items (plastic cards, tent cards), undated (Box 14)
  - Oversize Materials
    - Burrows presentation to Y&R, 1995 (Box OV1)
    - Flow charts, undated (Box OV1)
    - Forms, samples (WW), undated (Box OV1)
    - Surveys, samples, 1991 (Box OV1)
    - Printed Material
      - 575 Madison Avenue, circa 1950s (Box OV1)
      - Articles about Wunderman (Advertising Age, Campaign Direct), 1993-1998 (Box OV1)
      - Advertising Age, Y&R at 75, 1998 (Box OV1)
      - Live from 575 (WRK), 1983 (Box OV1)
      - One World (WCJ), circa 1995 (Box OV1)
      - Wunderama 1-6, 1996-1997 (Box OV1)
    - Training
      - Miscellaneous creative samples, 1986-1998 (Box OV1)
      - Y&R--Clockwise the Game, game board, undated (Box OV1)
    - Restricted Materials
      Restrictions on Access: Unpublished materials are closed to non-Wunderman researchers for 15 years from the date of creation.
      - Impiric--The I newsletter, 2000 (Box OV1)
      - WCJ newsletters, 1999-2000 (Box OV1)
      - Wunderama 7-9, 1998 (Box OV1)
  - Restricted Materials
    - Impiric
      - Beyond Ginsu: Principles of Winning Direct Response Television, circa 2000 (Box R1)
      - Building Global Capabilities: GHR/MarComm strategy update, circa 2000 (Box R1)
      - Customer Relationships, 2000, (2 folders) (Box R1)
      - Database marketing services, 2000 (Box R1)
      - E-Brain Market Research, 2000 (Box R1)
      - Global Recruiting Solutions, 2000, (2 folders) (Box R1)
      - Global Human Resources Job Descriptions, 2000, (1-2 of 4 folders) (Box R1)
      - Global Human Resources Job Descriptions, 2000, (3-4 of 4 folders) (Box R2)
      - Lead Qualification Opportunities, 2000 (Box R2)
      - Marketing Lab, 2000, (4 folders) (Box R2)
      - Topline Credentials, 2000 (Box R2)
    - WPP Group USA
      - Domestic and International Relocation Policies and Procedures, 2001, (3 folders) (Box R2)
    - Wunderman
      - ARBOS case study, 2001 (Box R2)
      - IBM Global Leadership Team Meeting, 2002, (2 folders) (Box R3)
      - Job Descriptions, 2000 (Box R3)
      - Temporary Transfer Program, 2002 (Box R3)
    - Wunderman Cato Johnson (WCJ)
      - Cinque Studio, 1999 (Box R3)
      - Credentials, 1999 (Box R3)
      - Employment--New Hires, 1995 (Box R3)
      - Worldwide Identity Standards, 1998 (Box R3)
    - Young & Rubicam (Y&R)
      - Creative Library requests, 1998-2000, (2 folders) (Box R3)
- Account Files, 1964-2001 and undated, (126 boxes)
  Includes case studies, campaign analyses, examples of campaign materials and creative work, memoranda and other documentation relating to Wunderman's work for its clients. The series focuses primarily on the United States and North America but some international work is represented here as well. Other international client activity is documented in the International Offices Series. Arranged alphabetically by client name.
  - General Files, 1980s-1996 and undated
    - International case studies, 1990-1996, (2 folders) (Box AF1)
    - Memoranda and communications, 1994-1996 (Box AF1)
    - Miscellaneous case studies: U.S. Army/AT&T/USPS, undated (Box AF1)
    - Photoboards, 1980s, (1-3 of 4 folders) (Box AF1)
    - Photoboards, 1980s (continued), (4 of 4 folders) (Box AF2)
    - The Creative Process, undated (Box AF2)
    - Transparencies: Adidas/Gillette/Taco Bell/USPS/Gevalia (Box AF2)
  - Active Apparel Group
    - General files, 1997 and undated (Box AF2)
  - AeroMexico
    - Brochure, undated (Box AF2)
  - Air France
    - General files, 1990-1995, (3 folders) (Box AF2)
    - Mailing
      - Bombardier, 1994 (Box AF2)
      - Business Fast Concorde Upgade, Hyatt Hotel Offer, 1994 (Box AF2)
      - Concorde, 1993-1996, (3 folders) (Box AF2)
      - Cruise, 1993 (Box AF2)
      - Euro Pass, 1994 (Box AF2)
      - Evian Festival, 1994 (Box AF2)
      - Executive Europe Transportation, 1992 (Box AF3)
      - Frequence Plus, 1994-1996, (5 folders) (Box AF3)
      - Holiday Chocolate, 1994 (Box AF3)
      - Holiday Mail, 1996 (Box AF3)
      - Housecleaning, 1992 (Box AF3)
      - IMAX, 1995 (Box AF3)
      - Jessue Norman, 1994 (Box AF3)
      - Just Savoir Faire, 1993 (Box AF3)
      - Kemwell, 1992 (Box AF3)
      - La Bistro D'a Cote (Free Dinner), 1992 (Box AF3)
      - L'espace launch, 1995 (Box AF3)
      - Louvre, 1993 (Box AF3)
      - Mailing with Premier & Savoir, 1993 (Box AF3)
      - Miscellaneous, 1994-1997, (3 folders) (Box AF4)
      - Meridien Nice Hotel discount, 1993 (Box AF4)
      - Michael Rostang--Free Dinner, 1993 (Box AF4)
      - Mileage accrual charge, 1993 (Box AF4)
      - Nina Ricci, 1994 (Box AF4)
      - Petanque, 1993 (Box AF4)
      - Purchase Ticket with AMEX, Companion Flies Free, 1994 (Box AF4)
      - Savoir Faire introduction, 1992 (Box AF4)
      - Tennis tournament, 1994 (Box AF4)
      - Terminal 2C--Gateway to the World, 1993 (Box AF4)
    - Printed material
      - Concorde Upgrade, 1996 (Box AF5)
      - Miscellaneous, 1994-1995 (Box AF5)
      - Savoir Faire, 1994-1995 (Box AF5)
  - Air New Zealand (LA/Bowes Dentsu)
    - General files, 1994 (Box AF5)
  - Alamo (Miami)
    - Alamo Small Business, 1996 (Box AF5)
    - Alamo True Blue, 1996-1999, (2 folders) (Box AF5)
    - Consumer mail, 1996 (Box AF5)
    - Europe Segment, 1996 (Box AF5)
  - Allied Signal (Detroit)
    - General files, 1996 and undated (Box AF5)
  - American Airlines
    - General files, 1984 and undated (Box AF5)
  - American Automobile Association (JCW Detroit)
    - General files, 1986 (Box AF5)
    - Mailers, 1986 (Box AF5)
  - American Bell
    - Mailing, 1982 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AF6)
    - Printed material, 1982 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AF6)
  - American Express
    - Account files (Box AF7)
    - Account review, 1987 (Box AF7)
    - American Automobile Association (AAA) tie-in, undated (Box AF7)
    - Case studies, 1990-1995 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AF7)
    - Competitor credit card brochures, 1987 and undated (Box AF7)
    - Corporate Card
      - Advertising, 1988-1996 (Box AF7)
      - Case study and miscellaneous, 1994 and undated (Box AF7)
      - Historical perspective, 1993 (Box AF7)
      - Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box AF7)
      - Photoboard, 1994 (Box AF7)
      - Presentation script, undated (Box AF7)
      - Relaunch, undated (Box AF7)
      - Sprint tie-in, 1995 (Box AF7)
      - Team Corporate Card, 1994, (2 folders) (Box AF7)
    - Custom Extras, 1997, (2 folders) (Box AF8)
    - Delta Skymiles credit card, 1995 (Box AF8)
    - Financial Direct case study, 1997 (Box AF8)
    - Fortune article, 1991 (Box AF8)
    - Gold Card
      - Report, 1988 (Box AF8)
    - Members of Distinction, 1991 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AF8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994-1996 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AF8)
    - Miscellaneous creative, 1987-1997 (Box AF8)
    - Newspaper advertising, 1989-1990 (Box AF8)
    - Optima Card
      - General, 1989-1992, (3 folders) (Box AF8)
      - Activity report, 1993 (Box AF9)
      - Advertising not produced by Wunderman, 1994 and undated (Box AF9)
      - Benefits brochures, 1994-1995 (Box AF9)
      - Case studies, undated (Box AF9)
      - Creative, analyses, 1987-1995 and undated, (5 folders) (Box AF9)
      - Loyalty program, 1993 (Box AF9)
      - Optima Card carriers, 1993 (Box AF9)